(Priya:)It means I-I work late.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Please tell me
you're not dating an American.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)I knew this would happen.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Rajesh, are you
letting your sister
(Mrs Koothrappali:)date that little Howard boy?
(Dr Koothrappali:)Now, hold on. If she
is dating an American,
(Dr Koothrappali:)that's not a bad way to go.
(Dr Koothrappali:)He's Jewish.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Those chaps are
very successful,
(Dr Koothrappali:)and they don't drink a lot.
It-It doesn't matter.
Howard has a girlfriend.
(Priya:)For now.
What does that mean?
(Priya:)I'll tell you later.
(Raj:)Is something going on
with him and Bernadette?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Who's Bernadette?
Doesn't sound Jewish.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)You can't tell by that.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Winona Ryder is Jewish.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Okay, we're getting
off the subject.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Rajesh, I want
you to try harder
(Dr Koothrappali:)to make your sister
feel welcome.
(Priya:)Thank you, Daddy.
(Raj:)Don't worry. Everything I have,
I share with her.
(Raj:)Including my friend Leon...
(Priya:)Good night, Mummy.
Good night, Daddy.
(Raj:)Oh, my God,
I think you broke my toe!
(Priya:)You should have kept
your mouth shut.
(Raj:)Fair enough.
(Raj:)Now, what's up with Clarinet...?
Bernadette!